const Castesim = [
	{
		questionText: 'Who said that Casteism that goes along with the benefit of the caste?',
		ans: ['Phanikkar'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who wrote the book "Caste in Indian Politics"?',
		ans: ['Rajneesh Kothari'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'In which State highest honour killings are reported?',
		ans: ['Haryana'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which State has reported highest crimes against Scheduled Castes as per NCRB 2020?',
		ans: ['Uttar Pradesh'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who said that Caste can be eradicated through inter-caste marriages and co- education?',
		ans: ['Ghurye'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Who said that Caste can be destroyed by creation of new values?',
		ans: ['PN Prabhu'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which organisation is providing incentive to the inter-caste marriage couple of Scheduled Castes and Scheduled Tribes?',
		ans: ['Ambedkar Foundation'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'In which year Karamchedu incident of attacks on Dalit took place?',
		ans: ['1985'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which incident has led to bring an act to prevent atrocities against Scheduled Castes and Scheduled Tribes?',
		ans: ['Karamehedu incident'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'In which State, Caste based private armies called as Ranvir Sena were formed?',
		ans: ['Bihar'],
	},
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },
];

export default Castesim;
